Guide to the Alfred Stieglitz / Georgia O'Keeffe Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Georgia O'Keeffe: Correspondence, 1907-86; Series VIII; 24.2; (58 boxes)
  - PERSONAL AND BUSINESS CORRESPONDENCE
    - Raymond and Raymond, Inc.
      See: Margery Crawford, Box 188, folder 3155
    - Read, Howard
    - Reich, Sheldon, 1964-72 (Box 210, Folder 3683)
    - Reid, William ("Ted"), 1951-83 (Box 210, Folder 3684)
    - Reilly, Richard, 1965, 1968 (Box 210, Folder 3685)
    - Research Ranch, Inc., 1974 (Box 210, Folder 3686)
    - Rhoades, Katharine, 1923-35 (Box 210, Folder 3687)
    - Rich, Bertha and children, 1949-66 (Box 210, Folder 3688)
    - Rich, Daniel Catton, 1970-76 (Box 210, Folder 3689)
      See also: Art Institute of Chicago (1941-58), Box 179, folders 2973-2978
      See also: Alfred Hentzen, Box 195, folder 3329
      See also: Worcester Art Museum, Box 220, folders 3928-3929
    - Rich, Sheldon
      See: Santa Fe Chamber Music Festival, Box 213, folders 3747-3749
    - Richter, Marga, 1974, 1976 (Box 210, Folder 3690)
    - Ridley, Gregory
      See: Fisk University (1985), Box 190, folders 3229-3231
    - Roach, Genevieve D., 1963-85, n.d. (Box 210, Folder 3691-3692)
    - Robbins, LeRoy, 1973 (Box 211, Folder 3693)
    - Robert Miller Gallery, 1976-86 (Box 211, Folder 3694)
      See also: Wadsworth Atheneum, Box 218, folder 3869
    - Roberts, Dudley, 1926-30 (Box 211, Folder 3695)
    - Roberts, F. W., 1954, 1956 (Box 211, Folder 3696)
    - Robertson, Gail, 1971-85, n.d. (Box 211, Folder 3697)
    - Robertson, Virginia, 1975-82 (Box 211, Folder 3698)
    - Robinson, Vivian; Robinson, David, 1965-69 (Box 211, Folder 3699)
      Includes: typescript of article on O'Keeffe
    - Rockefeller, Godfrey, 1968-69 (Box 211, Folder 3700)
    - Rochester Folk Art Guild
    - Rodakiewicz, Henwar, 1933-76, n.d. (Box 211, Folder 3701-3709)
    - Rodakiewicz, Olga Kotchoukova, 1950-76 (Box 211, Folder 3710)
    - Rodale, Anna, 1967-68 (Box 211, Folder 3711)
    - Rolf, Ida P., 1964-78 (Box 211, Folder 3712)
    - Rolf Institute, 1976-84 (Box 211, Folder 3713)
    - Rolf Nelson Gallery, 1964-69 (Box 211, Folder 3714)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1944 Feb 10 (Box 211, Folder 3715)
    - Rose, Barbara, 1976 (Box 211, Folder 3716)
    - Rosen, Jack, 1969-83 (Box 212, Folder 3717)
      Includes: caricature of Robert Young
    - Rosen, Louis: offprints, 1970-80 (Box 212, Folder 3718)
    - Rosen, Mary and Louis, 1971-84, n.d. (Box 212, Folder 3719)
    - Rosenbaum, Ella and Paul, 1967-77, n.d. (Box 212, Folder 3720)
    - Rosenblum, Naomi, 1975-79 (Box 212, Folder 3721)
    - Rosenfeld, Paul, 1921-45 (Box 212, Folder 3722)
    - Ross, Cary, 1940, 1951, n.d. (Box 212, Folder 3723)
    - Ross, Gloria F., 1970-77 (Box 212, Folder 3724)
    - Rossin, Clara, 1927 (Box 212, Folder 3725)
    - Roswell Museum and Art Center, 1962, 1968 (Box 212, Folder 3726)
    - Rubenstein, Meridel, 1974-75 (Box 212, Folder 3727)
      Includes: seminar paper on O'Keeffe and Stieglitz
    - "S" general, 1950-85, n.d. (Box 212, Folder 3728-3731)
    - St. Andrew's Episcopal Day School (Jacksonville, FL), 1974-77 (Box 212, Folder 3732)
    - St. Dominic's School (San Francisco, CA), 1971 (Box 212, Folder 3733)
    - St. John's College, 1965-77, n.d. (Box 212, Folder 3734)
    - Saint Joseph College, 1960-63 (Box 212, Folder 3735)
    - St. Louis Art Museum, 1944-45, n.d. (Box 212, Folder 3736)
    - St. Peter's School (Geneva, IL), 1983 (Box 212, Folder 3737)
    - St. Thomas Apostle, Abiquiu, 1981-83 (Box 212, Folder 3738)
    - Saarinen, Aline, 1964, n.d. (Box 213, Folder 3739)
    - San Diego Museum of Art, 1981-86 (Box 213, Folder 3740)
    - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1954-72 (Box 213, Folder 3741)
    - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1974-85, n.d. (Box 213, Folder 3742-3743)
    - Sanders, Ben T. and Alison Sanders, Ursula, 1964-80, n.d. (Box 213, Folder 3744)
    - Sandoval, Carmel, 1971 (Box 213, Folder 3745)
    - Santa Barbara Museum, 1950 (Box 213, Folder 3746)
    - Santa Fe Chamber Music Festival: correspondence, 1973-86 (Box 213, Folder 3747-3749)
    - Santa Fe Chamber Music Festival: concert programs, 1973-85 (Box 213, Folder 3750-3751)
    - Santa Fe Festival Theatre, 1981 (Box 213, Folder 3752)
    - Sarkesian, Carol, 1974, 1976, n.d. (Box 213, Folder 3753)
    - Schauffler, Bennet and Marie, 1968-78 (Box 213, Folder 3754)
    - Schauffler, Florence M., 1917 Apr 10 (Box 213, Folder 3755)
    - Schubart, Dorothy Obermeyer, 1965-84, n.d. (Box 213, Folder 3756)
    - Schubart, Howard
      See: William Einstein (Mar 1952), Boxes 189-190, folders 3204-3212
    - Schutzbank, Madeline, 1952 May 16 (Box 213, Folder 3757)
    - Schwab, Arthur, 1924-63, n.d. (Box 213, Folder 3758)
    - Schwartz, Sanford, 1976-82, n.d. (Box 213, Folder 3759)
    - Scott, Cecil, 1950 (Box 213, Folder 3760)
    - Scottish National Gallery of Modern Art, 1983 (Box 213, Folder 3761)
      See also: Metropolitan Museum of Art (1983), Box 202, folders 3503-3508
    - Sebring, June O'Keeffe; Sebring, Frank, 1950-84 (Box 214, Folder 3762)
    - Seeger, Joachim F., 1952 (Box 214, Folder 3763)
    - Seldis, Henry J.
      See: Los Angeles Times, Box 200, folder 3446
    - Seligmann, Herbert J. and Lise; Seligmann, Lilias, 1928-78, n.d. (Box 214, Folder 3764-3765)
    - Seth, Jean and Oliver, 1964-80, n.d. (Box 214, Folder 3766)
    - Seth, Sandy; Seth, Laurie, 1968-84, n.d. (Box 214, Folder 3767)
    - Shaklee Corporation, 1981-82 (Box 214, Folder 3768)
    - Shansby, Gary
      See: Shaklee Corporation, Box 214, folder 3768
    - Sheldon, Huntingdon, 1980 (Box 214, Folder 3769)
    - Shonnard, Eugenie, 1963-69 (Box 214, Folder 3770)
    - Shorewood Hills School (Madison, WI), 1983 (Box 214, Folder 3771)
    - Shriver, Eunice Kennedy, 1968 Sep 26 (Box 214, Folder 3772)
    - Sickman, Laurence; Baldwin, James, 1956-70, n.d. (Box 214, Folder 3773)
    - Sidney Janis Gallery, 1955-83 (Box 214, Folder 3774)
    - Sierra Club, 1973-85 (Box 214, Folder 3775)
    - Sills, Philip, 1970-78 (Box 214, Folder 3776)
    - Singham, S. Durai Raja, 1971-74, n.d. (Box 214, Folder 3777)
    - Skeen, Joe, 1981 (Box 214, Folder 3778)
    - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture, 1972-84 (Box 214, Folder 3779-3780)
      See also: Margaret McDermott, Box 201, folder 3463
    - Slick, Charles U.
      See: Martina Yamin, Box 221, folder 3940
    - Sloane, T. O'Conor
      See: Doubleday, Box 188, folder 3184
    - Smith, Andrew, 1978-79 (Box 214, Folder 3781)
    - Smith College Library, 1960 (Box 214, Folder 3782)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1976-77 (Box 214, Folder 3783)
    - Smithsonian Magazine, 1980 (Box 214, Folder 3784)
    - Soby, James Thrall, 1946, 1954 (Box 214, Folder 3785)
    - Solomon, Joseph, 1963-77 (Box 214, Folder 3786)
    - Spanish Riding School (Vienna), 1971-72 (Box 214, Folder 3787)
    - Speicher, Eugene, 1915 Jan 6 (Box 214, Folder 3788)
    - Speyer, Dorothea
      See: Lawrence Calcagno, Box 183, folder 3052
    - Speyer, James, 1974-82 (Box 214, Folder 3789)
    - Stauffer, Pauline, 1960-77 (Box 214, Folder 3790)
    - Stearns, Milton S., Jr., 1972 Nov 22 (Box 214, Folder 3791)
    - Stebbins, Theodore, 1973 Jan 5 (Box 214, Folder 3792)
    - Steichen, Edward, 1953-69 (Box 214, Folder 3793)
    - Stein, Leo, n.d. (Box 214, Folder 3794)
    - Steiner, Daniel and family, 1973, 1975 (Box 214, Folder 3795)
    - Steloff, Frances
      See: Gotham Book Mart, Box 193, folder 3278
    - Stettheimer, Ettie, 1925-54, n.d. (Box 215, Folder 3796-3798)
      See also: Frances O'Brien (1952), Box 206, folder 3601
    - Stettheimer, Florine, 1928 Oct 21 (Box 215, Folder 3799)
    - Steullet, Cecile
      See: Jean Ledoux, Box 199, folders 3423-3424
    - Stewart, David Charles, 1963 Sep 25 (Box 215, Folder 3800)
    - Stieglitz, Alfred
      See: Mabel Dodge Luhan, Box 200, folder 3451
      See: Karl Struss, Box 215, folder 3809
    - Stieglitz, Edward J., 1948 Dec 30 (Box 215, Folder 3801)
    - Stieglitz, Jean, 1961-70 (Box 215, Folder 3802)
    - Stieglitz, Leopold, 1948, 1951 (Box 215, Folder 3803)
    - Stix, Emma K., 1926, n.d. (Box 215, Folder 3804)
    - Stoddard, Helen, 1961 (Box 215, Folder 3805)
    - Stokowski, Leopold, 1969 Dec 8 (Box 215, Folder 3806)
    - Stoumen, Louis Clyde, 1955-57 (Box 215, Folder 3807)
    - Straus, Flora Stieglitz, 1954-73 (Box 215, Folder 3808)
    - Struss, Karl, 1977 (Box 215, Folder 3809)
    - Suazo, Jackie, 1953-56, 1983 (Box 215, Folder 3810)
    - Subhana and Sons, 1960 (Box 215, Folder 3811)
    - Sun Prarie Historical Society, 1972-73 (Box 215, Folder 3812)
    - Sutherland, Ruth
      See: Anita Pollitzer (1951), Boxes 208-209, folders 2646-3662
    - Swanson, Rodney, n.d. (Box 215, Folder 3813)
    - Sweeney, James Johnson and Laura, 1945-76, n.d. (Box 215, Folder 3814-3815)
      See also: J. Robert Oppenheimer Memorial Committee, Box 196, folder 3364
      See also: Museum of Modern Art (1945-46), Box 204, folders 3545-3546
    - Sweeney, Seán, 1965-77 (Box 215, Folder 3816)
      See also: James Sweeney (1970), Box 215, folders 3814-3815
    - Sykes, Gerald, 1966-84 (Box 215, Folder 3817-3818)
    - "T" general, 1968-84, n.d. (Box 215, Folder 3819)
    - Taft Museum, 1950 (Box 215, Folder 3820)
    - Tahk, Christopher, 1978 Nov 22 (Box 215, Folder 3821)
    - Tamarind Lithography Workshop, Inc., 1964, 1966, n.d. (Box 215, Folder 3822)
    - Tawney, Lenore, 1968-73 (Box 215, Folder 3823)
    - Terra Museum of American Art, 1986 (Box 216, Folder 3824)
    - Terry Dintenfass, Inc., 1963-64 (Box 216, Folder 3825)
    - Texas Tech University, 1967-71 (Box 216, Folder 3826)
      See also: Frances Holden, Box 195, folder 3338
    - Thuma, Marilynn, 1964-73, n.d. (Box 216, Folder 3827)
    - Time
      See: Leo Janos, Box 196, folder 3367
    - Tofel, Jennings, 1924 Jan 3 (Box 216, Folder 3828)
    - Toledo Museum of Art, 1975-76 (Box 216, Folder 3829)
    - Tomkins, Calvin; Tomkins, Judy
      See: Cunningham Dance Foundation, Box 188, folders 3161
      See: The New Yorker, Box 206, folder 3587
    - Tomlinson, Charles and Brenda, 1964, 1979, n.d. (Box 216, Folder 3830)
    - Toomer, Jean, 1924-49 (Box 216, Folder 3831)
    - Toomer, Marjorie
      See: Marjorie Content, Box 187, folder 3144
    - Totto, Katharine ("Kay") Luse and daughters, 1960-84, n.d. (Box 216, Folder 3832)
      See also: Francis O'Keeffe (1960), Box 206, folders 3596-3598
    - Trask, Gladys, 1960-73 (Box 216, Folder 3833)
    - True, Dorothy
      See: Anita Pollitzer (1917), Boxes 208-209, folders 2646-3662
    - Truitt, Jim, 1967, 1969, n.d. (Box 216, Folder 3834)
    - Trujillo, Vivian, 1964-79, n.d. (Box 216, Folder 3835)
    - Trust for Public Land: correspondence, 1980-85 (Box 216, Folder 3836)
    - Trust for Public Land: publications, 1979-86 (Box 216, Folder 3837)
    - Tryk, Sheila Cameron
      See: New Mexico Magazine, Box 206, folder 3580
    - Tuchman, Barbara, 1976, 1984 (Box 216, Folder 3838)
    - Twelvetrees Press, 1983 (Box 216, Folder 3839)
    - Tyler, Kenneth, 1975 Dec 29 (Box 216, Folder 3840)
      See also: Gemini G.E.L., Box 191, folder 3250
    - "U" general, 1950-85, n.d. (Box 216, Folder 3841)
    - UNICEF, 1973-83 (Box 216, Folder 3842)
    - United States. Embassy (France), 1963 (Box 216, Folder 3843)
    - United States Information Agency, 1953-56 (Box 216, Folder 3844)
    - United States. Department of State., 1957-77 (Box 216, Folder 3845)
      See also: New York Times, Box 206, folder 3583
    - United States. National Park Service: correspondence, 1971-84 (Box 216, Folder 3846-3847)
    - United States. National Park Service: studies for proposed Georgia O'Keeffe National Historic Site, 1979 (Box 216, Folder 3848)
    - United States. National Park Service: plans for other sites, 1971-80 (Box 217, Folder 3849-3851)
      Includes: development concept plans and master plans for Hubbell, Saint Gaudens, Sandburg, Bandelier, and Johnson National Historic Sites
    - United States. President., 1965-85 (Box 217, Folder 3852)
      Contains routine correspondence with office personnel
    - University of Dallas
      See: Margaret McDermott, Box 210, folder 3463
    - University of Georgia, 1946 (Box 217, Folder 3853)
    - University of Minnesota, 1938 May 9 (Box 217, Folder 3854)
    - University of New Mexico, 1963-78 (Box 217, Folder 3855)
    - University of New Mexico Art Museum, 1963-80 (Box 217, Folder 3856)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1966-84, n.d. (Box 217, Folder 3857)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1961-70 (Box 217, Folder 3858)
    - "V" general, 1960-84 (Box 217, Folder 3859)
    - Van Vechten, Carl, 1940-65, n.d. (Box 217, Folder 3860)
    - Vanderpoel, John H., 1907 Apr 24 (Box 217, Folder 3861)
    - Vedder, Alan
      See: Museum of New Mexico (1966-67), Box 204, folders 3547-3548
    - Victoria and Albert Museum, 1981-83 (Box 217, Folder 3862)
    - Viking Press, Inc., 1974-83 (Box 217, Folder 3863-3864)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1985 (Box 217, Folder 3865)
    - Vogue, 1966, 1983 (Box 217, Folder 3866)
    - Volkmer, Jean
      See: Box 222, folder 3962
    - "W" general, 1960-85, n.d. (Box 217, Folder 3867-3868)
    - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1980-86 (Box 218, Folder 3869)
    - Wadsworth, Cleone, 1957 (Box 218, Folder 3870)
    - Waintrob, Sidney
      See: Budd Studio, Box 182, folder 3041
    - Walker Art Center, 1959-71 (Box 218, Folder 3871)
    - Walker, Jim, 1966-67 (Box 218, Folder 3872)
      Includes: paper on O'Keeffe
    - Walker, Sybil, 1949-69 (Box 218, Folder 3873)
    - Wall, Aelred, 1976-84, n.d. (Box 218, Folder 3874)
    - Wallace, Amei, 1977 (Box 218, Folder 3875)
    - Wallace, David D., 1984-85 (Box 218, Folder 3876)
    - Warhol, Andy, 1980 (Box 218, Folder 3877)
      Includes: galley of interview with O'Keeffe
    - Washington International Arts Letter, 1967, n.d. (Box 218, Folder 3878)
    - Watkins, Kindred M., 1917 May 6 (Box 218, Folder 3879)
    - Wayne, June, 1972-80, n.d. (Box 218, Folder 3880)
      See also: Tamarind Lithography Workshop, Box 215, folder 3822
    - Webb, Lucile, 1956-67 (Box 218, Folder 3881)
    - Webb, Todd, 1952-86, n.d. (Box 218, Folder 3882-3885)
    - Weber, Bruce, 1980 Sep 12 (Box 218, Folder 3886)
    - Wehrheim, John, 1974, n.d. (Box 218, Folder 3887)
    - Weiss, Aline Pollitzer, 1916-17 (Box 218, Folder 3888)
    - Weiss, Ray L., n.d. (Box 218, Folder 3889)
    - Wells, Cady, 1937-53, n.d. (Box 218, Folder 3890)
    - Wells, Mason B., 1955-82 (Box 218, Folder 3891)
    - Wertheim, Alma M.; Wertheim, Maurice, 1922, n.d. (Box 218, Folder 3892)
    - Wescott, Glenway, 1968, 1970 (Box 218, Folder 3893)
    - West Texas State Normal College, 1916-18, 1950 (Box 218, Folder 3894)
    - West Texas State University, 1977-83 (Box 218, Folder 3895)
      See also: Roberta Brosseau, Box 182, folder 3029
    - Wheelwright Museum of the American Indian, 1969-83 (Box 218, Folder 3896)
    - White House
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1946-86, n.d. (Box 219, Folder 3897-3902)
    - Who's Who, Inc., 1969-76 (Box 219, Folder 3903)
    - Wichita Art Museum, 1979-80 (Box 219, Folder 3904)
    - Wight, Frederick S., 1954-77, n.d. (Box 219, Folder 3905)
    - Wildenstein & Company, 1973 Mar 19 (Box 219, Folder 3906)
    - Wilder, Elizabeth, 1962 (Box 219, Folder 3907)
    - Wilder, Mitchell; Wilder, Sally, 1953-72, n.d. (Box 219, Folder 3908)
      See also: Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, Box 187, folder 3136
    - The Wilderness Society, 1985 Sep 12 (Box 219, Folder 3909)
    - Willard, Charlotte, 1960-68 (Box 219, Folder 3910)
    - Williamsburg (VA) Public Schools, 1911 May 11 (Box 219, Folder 3911)
    - Wilson, Bee, 1961-77, n.d. (Box 219, Folder 3912)
    - Wilson, Claggett, 1923 (Box 219, Folder 3913)
    - Wilson, Margaret: transcript of fragment of letter to E. Davidson, 1940 (Box 219, Folder 3914)
    - Wilson, Mildred P., 1968 Mar 31 (Box 219, Folder 3915)
    - Witschi, Frederick, 1960-77 (Box 219, Folder 3916)
    - Witte Memorial Museum, 1964 Jan 20 (Box 219, Folder 3917)
    - WNET/13, 1971-77 (Box 219, Folder 3918-3919)
    - WNET/13, 1978-85 (Box 220, Folder 3920-3921)
    - Wofford, Harris L., 1979-83 (Box 220, Folder 3922)
      See also: Bryn Mawr College, Box 182, folder 3037
    - Wood, Margaret, 1983, 1985 (Box 220, Folder 3923)
    - Wood, Sally, 1968-73 (Box 220, Folder 3924)
    - Woodruff, Helen, 1959-80, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 3925-3926)
    - Woolley, John Carrington, 1978 (Box 220, Folder 3927)
    - Worcester Art Museum, 1958-69 (Box 220, Folder 3928-3929)
      See also: The Downtown Gallery (1960), Box 189, folder 3188-3190
    - Workman, David, 1961-70, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 3930)
    - Worth, Don, 1958-64 (Box 220, Folder 3931)
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1933-47 (Box 220, Folder 3932)
    - Wright, Olgivanna Lloyd, 1960-73 (Box 220, Folder 3933)
    - "Y" general, 1969-86 (Box 220, Folder 3934)
    - Yale University Art Gallery, 1965, 1984 (Box 220, Folder 3935)
    - Yale University Library, 1952-76 (Box 220, Folder 3936-3937)
    - Yale University Library, 1977-85 (Box 221, Folder 3938-3939)
    - Yamanaka, Shoji, 1969, 1972 (Box 221, Folder 3940)
    - Yamin, Martina
      See: Box 222, folder 3963
    - Yanike, Alice Rose, 1953-55, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 3941)
    - Yates, Sidney R., 1980, 1983 (Box 221, Folder 3942)
    - York, Richard T.
      See: Fisk University (1980-81), Box 190, folders 3229-3231
    - Young, Anita O'Keeffe, 1949-85, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 3943-3945)
    - Young, Robert R., 1950-51 (Box 221, Folder 3946)
    - "Z" general, 1968-74, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 3947)
    - Ziegler, Samuel and Isabel, 1962-78, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 3948)
    - Zigrosser, Carl, 1924 Sep 4 (Box 221, Folder 3949)
      See also: Philadelphia Museum of Art, Box 208, folders 3633-3634
    - Zuccari, Frank
      See: Box 222, folder 3964
    - Zucker, Barbara Cohen, 1967-68, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 3950)
    - Employment inquiries, 1980-85, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 3951)
    - Unidentified correspondents: Gus, 1937-46 (Box 221, Folder 3952)
    - Unidentified correspondents, miscellaneous: incoming, 1917-83, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 3953)
    - Unidentified correspondents: outgoing, 1937, 1976-77, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 3954)
  - SUBJECT FILES
    - Conservation of Paintings
      Includes: correspondence with conservators, as well as condition and treatment proposals and reports prepared for owners (O'Keeffe and others) of O'Keeffe paintings
      - Fine Arts Conservation Laboratories, Inc., 1961-63 (Box 222, Folder 3955)
      - Hines, Felrath, 1966-79, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 3956)
      - Keck, Caroline and Sheldon, 1950-83, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 3957-3959)
      - King, Antoinette, 1974-75 (Box 222, Folder 3960)
      - Mayer, Lance, 1977 (Box 222, Folder 3961)
      - Volkmer, Jean, 1970-85 (Box 222, Folder 3962)
      - Yamin, Martina, 1980 (Box 222, Folder 3963)
      - Zuccari, Frank, 1977 (Box 222, Folder 3964)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia
      - Biographical material
        - Review of her exhibition at Intimate Gallery, typescript, 1928 Mar (Box 222, Folder 3965)
        - "O'Keeffe" from Masters in Modern Art, by James Lane; typescript transcript with carbon, [1936] (Box 222, Folder 3966)
        - Transcript of radio interview with Adelaide Hawley, mimeograph, 1940 Mar (Box 222, Folder 3967)
        - Resume, typescript carbons and photocopy, 1963 Aug (Box 222, Folder 3968)
        - "The Formative Years: Sun Prairie, Wisconsin and Williamsburg, Virginia" by unidentified author, [1973] (Box 222, Folder 3969)
        - "The Influence of the Texas Panhandle on Georgia O'Keeffe," by John F. Matthews, photocopy, 1983 (Box 222, Folder 3970)
        - Copy of Testimonials, 1907-11, typescript, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 3971)
        - "Georgia O'Keeffe" by Louise Goepfert March, typescript carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 3972)
        - Transcript of interview with Ilka Chase, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 3973)
        - Miscellaneous biographical essays, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 3974)
        - Her statements on her work, 1923, 1934, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 3975)
        - Her statement on her collection of Stieglitz photographs, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 3976)
    - Stieglitz, Alfred
      - Certificate of death (three official copies), 1946 Jul 17 (Box 222, Folder 3977)
      - Condolence letters received upon his death, 1946 (Box 222, Folder 3978)
        Includes: letters from Dorothy Brett, Frederick Mortimer Clapp, Eva Esmann, Mike Harding, Esther Johnson, Louise G. March, Yolla Niclas-Sachs, Anita Pollitzer, Eliot Porter, Daniel Rich, Ettie Stettheimer, Todd Webb, Frank Lloyd Wright, Carl Van Vechten.
      - Notes on art collection, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 3979)
      - Quotes by him, typed transcript, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 3980)
  - FAN MAIL
    - "From my show" [Museum of Modern Art], 1946 (Box 223, Folder 3981)
      Includes: letters from William Einstein, Alexander Eliot, Ellen Harrison, Fiske Kimball, A. Hyatt Mayor, "Ted" Reid, Yolla Niclas- Sachs, Selma Stieglitz Schubart, Bertram Smith, Ruth Steinway, Claggett Wilson, Carl Zigrosser.
    - Letters, 1934-68 (Box 223, Folder 3982-3994)
    - Letters, 1968 (Box 224, Folder 3995-4006)
    - Letters, 1969-70 (Box 225, Folder 4007-4017)
    - Letters, 1971 (Box 226, Folder 4018-4027)
    - Letters, 1972-74 (Box 227, Folder 4028-4039)
    - Letters, 1975-77 (Box 228, Folder 4040-4051)
    - Letters, 1977-83 (Box 229, Folder 4052-4066)
    - Letters, 1983 (Box 230, Folder 4067-4077)
    - Letters, 1984 (Box 231, Folder 4078-4087)
    - Letters, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 4088-4098)
    - Letters, 1985 (Box 233, Folder 4099-4102)
    - Letters, n.d. (Box 233, Folder 4103)
    - Form letter response to fan mail, [1969] (Box 233, Folder 4104)
    - Poems, 1968-82, n.d. (Box 233, Folder 4105-4108)
      Contains letters with enclosed poems written by fans; many more examples can be found throughout the folders of fan mail in this subseries.
  - RIGHTS AND REPRODUCTION CORRESPONDENCE
    - Requests, 1953-82 (Box 233, Folder 4109-4111)
    - Requests, 1983 (Box 234, Folder 4112-4115)
    - Requests, 1984 (Box 234, Folder 4116-4119)
    - Requests, 1985 (Box 234, Folder 4120-4125)
    - Requests, n.d. (Box 234, Folder 4126)
- Georgia O'Keeffe: Documentary Ephemera, 1926-86; Series IX; 1.25; (3 boxes)
  The Series is arranged in three subseries: Clipping Files; Exhibition Ephemera; and Miscellaneous Ephemera.
  - CLIPPING FILES
    - About O'Keeffe and her work
      - General articles, 1926-81 (Box 235, Folder 4127-4132)
      - General articles: Architectural Digest, 1981 Jul (Box 235, Folder 4133)
      - General articles, 1982-86 (Box 235, Folder 4134)
      - General articles: Artspace, 1986 (Box 235, Folder 4135)
      - General articles, n.d. (Box 235, Folder 4136)
      - Book Reviews
        - Autobiography, 1976, 1978 (Box 235, Folder 4137-4139)
        - Lisle biography, 1980-81 (Box 235, Folder 4140)
        - Miscellaneous, 1969-84, n.d. (Box 235, Folder 4141)
      - Exhibitions, 1926-85, n.d. (Box 236, Folder 4142-4147)
      - Reproductions of Her Work, 1949-68 (Box 236, Folder 4148)
      - Miscellaneous, 1945-84, n.d. (Box 236, Folder 4149-4150)
    - About People and Topics of Interest
      - Calder, Alexander, 1976 (Box 236, Folder 4151)
      - Dove, Arthur, 1971 (Box 236, Folder 4152)
      - Fisk University, 1950, 1984 (Box 236, Folder 4153)
      - Garson, Greer, 1968 (Box 236, Folder 4154)
      - Halpert, Edith - sale, 1973 (Box 236, Folder 4155)
      - McGovern, George, 1972 (Box 236, Folder 4156)
      - Marin, John, 1958 (Box 236, Folder 4157)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1967-73 (Box 236, Folder 4158)
      - Newhall, Beaumont, 1979 (Box 236, Folder 4159)
      - Ravagli, Angelino, 1972 (Box 236, Folder 4160)
      - Rothko decision, 1970-76 (Box 236, Folder 4161)
      - Steichen, Edward, 1963 (Box 236, Folder 4162)